This guy became a billionaire just by solving his own problems. Here's how.
A few years ago, he and his roommate Joe couldn't afford to pay their rent.
So they pumped up three air mattresses and started a bed and breakfast.
And today he put out tweets. But on the surface, seems pretty
normal. But underneath it, I think, has a load of wisdom if you're
an entrepreneur or a content creator. In fact, Naval rubber cunt who's a millionaire,
put out this tweet about the same idea. And when I looked back at
growing my YouTube channel to 6000 subscribers, I realized
I did it through solving my own problems and then sharing the
solution. And the biggest mistake that creators and entrepreneurs make
is making something that people don't really want.
The way you avoid that is by solving your own problems and then sharing
in the solution. If it's a problem that you had will be other people
that had the same problem and therefore want the solution. And that
is how.